https://dev.openinventionnetwork.com/privacy-policy/

Corporate Overview
Why OIN?
Linux System Definition
Search for:
Privacy Policy
Home|Privacy Policy
Privacy Policyoin-admin2020-06-11T12:48:32+00:00
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Open Invention Network LLC (“OIN”) and our website openinventionnetwork.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We only collect information that you voluntarily give us via our website forms or via email or other direct contact from you.
We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill our obligations to you under the OIN license agreement.
If you opt in to our mailing list, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about news, conferences, and other matters such as changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email at info@openinventionnetwork.com:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit information via our electronic signature service, your information is protected both online and offline.
In our electronic signature service form, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only parties who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, licensing representatives and administrative officers for legal notices) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Electronic Signature and Related Forms
It is not required that organizations join the OIN community via our online electronic signature service, as organizations may mail in signed hardcopies of the OIN license agreement.  However, many organizations opt to do so for convenience.  To do so, a user at the organization must first complete online forms.  During the filling of these forms, a user is required to give certain information (such as name, email address, and title). Our electronic signature service also stamps your signed OIN license agreement with your IP address.  This information is used to verify the user’s identity and provide legal notices to your organization as required by the OIN license agreement.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at info@openinventionnetwork.com.
What People Say
UNISOC is committed to the independent development and design of core chips in the field of mobile communications and AIoT, and Linux and open source software are the key elements of our technology development. By joining the OIN community, Zhanrui demonstrates its strong commitment to innovation and will continue to support patent protection for projects such as Linux.
Yang Jiejing, Head of Legal DepartmentUNISOC
As a global solutions provider that grows with customers and society through the highest level of trust, SMFG is committed to creating businesses that transcend the boundaries of finance and resolving issues. In order to further promote this effort and quickly deliver high added-value services to our customers and society, SMFG believes that the utilization of open source software will be essential. Also, in promoting OSS utilization, SMFG believes that measures to protect intellectual property rights are important. Through joining the OIN, SMFG hopes to deepen our understanding of the OSS community and contribute to the development of OSS.
SMFG
Open source technology enables new levels of innovation and helps to underpin our ongoing growth, as we fuse physical and digital technologies in cyber-physical systems. By joining OIN, we are demonstrating our commitment to contribute to open source technology and supporting it with patent non-aggression in Linux.
Dr. Shiro Saito, Executive Officer, Corporate EVP, General Executive for TechnologyToshiba
Although TAIYO YUDEN does not directly incorporate open source software in our products, our customers do, and it is important for us to support open source initiatives that are critical to the continued success of our clients.
Shigetoshi Akino, General Manager, Intellectual Property DivisionTAIYO YUDEN
Huawei is committed to offering the highest-quality ICT and smart devices. Linux and OSS are critical elements of technologies we are developing and integrating with carriers and enterprises around the globe. By joining the Open Invention Network, we are demonstrating our continued commitment to innovation, and supporting it with patent non-aggression in Linux and other core open source projects.
Jianxin Ding, Head of Global Intellectual PropertyHuawei
The Mercari Group’s systems are supported by a variety of open source software. As a beneficiary of the enormous contributions made by the open source software community, we believe making a contribution to innovation in the world by publishing technology accumulated through the development and operation of our services, such as Mercari and Merpay, as open source is the right choice. Hence, the Mercari Group endorses the activities of OIN which protects innovations with open source from patent risks.
Mercari
At Rakuten, our businesses continue to evolve as we address new market opportunities. Because of this, we are a user and strong advocate of open source software. We are building the first 100% fully virtualized mobile network, enabling us to scale rapidly and offer the best Quality-of-Service (QoS) available. By joining OIN, we are demonstrating our commitment to Open Source Software (OSS) and supporting it with a pledge of patent non-aggression.
Tareq Amin, CAO, Group Executive Vice PresidentRakuten, Inc.
Today, with open source software, we are quickly creating robust and long-lasting solutions for our customers. In addition to the technical implementation, we also take care that our customers do not worry about potential license violations.”
Andreas Pfeiffer, Head of Customer Advice and MarketingGinzinger
Protecting open source is critical to us, our users and to the ongoing health of the Internet. We’re proud of our new role within OIN. We’re very happy with the direction OIN has been going.
Chris DiBona, Director of Open SourceGoogle
We believe the protection OIN offers the open source community helps increase global contributions to and adoption of open source technologies. We are honored to stand with OIN as an active participant in its program to protect against patent aggression in core Linux and other important OSS technologies.
Erich AndersenMicrosoft
Recently Joined Our Community
Research Triangle Park Center
4819 Emperor Blvd., Suite 400
Durham, NC 27703
Tel: +1 919-313-4902
info@openinventionnetwork.com
CONTACT US Licensing Team Representatives
Email*
Marketing ConsentOIN is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We are interested in sending OIN community news, educational, and marketing content that may be of interest to you. If you consent to us contacting you for this purpose, please tick below:
I agree to join OIN's marketing mailing list and to receive other communications from OIN.
You may unsubscribe from OIN's communications at any time. For more information on how to unsubscribe, our privacy practices, and how we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy, please review our Privacy Policy.
Subscribe Now
Copyright 2020 Open Invention Network | All Rights Reserved.
Go to Top
